你好，你们这些漂亮的人。
Hello you beautiful people.
欢迎收看这段视频。
And welcome to this video.
我们将在您的计算机上设置虚拟盒。
We're going to be getting you set up with virtual box on your computer.
现在，Virtual Box是一款令人惊叹的软件，它允许您运行所谓的虚拟机
Now virtual box is an amazing piece of software that allows you to run what are called virtual machines
在你的电脑上。
on your computer.
现在，除了有一个听起来非常棒的名称之外，虚拟机还允许您运行虚拟计算机
Now virtual machines other than having a totally awesome sounding name allow you to run virtual computers
在不影响实际计算机的情况下安装在您的计算机内，因此它们非常适合运行诸如
inside your computer without affecting your actual computer so they're perfect for running things like
新操作系统，并在不影响当前计算机工作方式的情况下试用它们
new operating systems and trying them out without affecting the way that your current computer works
因此，通过虚拟机器运行虚拟机将为我们创建完美的游乐场
so running a virtual machine through virtual box is going to create the perfect playground for us to
尝试使用影响您的实际计算机工作方式的Linux操作系统。
try the Linux operating system that is affecting the way that your actual computer works.
所以实际上不会出什么差错，所以这是我们试用该软件的完美场所。
So nothing can actually go wrong so it's the perfect playground for us to try out the software.
所以我想要做的总是去虚拟盒子网站，它不是虚拟盒子网站org
So what I want to do is always a head over to the Virtual Box website which is not virtual box dot org
用于维基下载。
for Wiki for downloads.
我在这段视频的资源部分放了一个链接，或者你可以直接拥有它，或者你可以直接
I put a link in the resources section for this video or you could just have it or you could just head
转到您最喜欢的搜索引擎，只需搜索Virtual Box下载，它很可能是
over to your favorite search engine and just search for Virtual Box download and it will likely be the
出现的第一个链接。
first link that comes up.
当你点击它的时候，你会看到一个这样的页面。
And when you click it you'll come to a page like this.
好的。
OK.
现在，您可以在这里找到一些指向某些特定的可执行安装程序文件的链接，我希望您
Now here you go find some some links to some specific executable installer files that I want you to
如果您使用Windows，请下载案例。如果您是Mac，请单击Windows主机，我们将单击
download a case if you're on Windows I want you to click Windows hosts if you're a Mac and we to click
OS10主机运行正常，如果您愿意，如果您已经在Linux上，那么基本上不需要安装Linux
OS 10 hosts OK and if you want if you're already on Linux you basically don't need to install Linux
这样你就可以跳过整个部分，转到实际学习的内容。
do you so you can just skip this entire section and move on to actual learning stuff.
但是我们在这里，如果你想要Windows，点击Windows，如果你在Mac上，我10岁，但我在Windows Sangli上
But here we are if you want Windows click Windows if you are on Mac I was 10 but I'm on Windows Sangli
单击该按钮，您可以在此处下载并安装文件。
click that and you can download and install a file here.
好的。
OK.
现在我要做的是将其保存在我的Downloads文件夹中，但您可以将其保存
Now what I'm going to do is I'm going to just save that in my downloads folder but you can save that
任何最适合你的地方，但我可以将它保存在我的下载文件夹中，它将被下载并安装。
wherever is best for you but I can save it in my downloads folder and it's going to download and install.
它将为我们安装虚拟盒子。
And it's going to install Virtual Box for us.
好的。
OK.
所以这将是头端下载，应该是在大约两秒钟内完成的。
So that's going to headend downloaded what should be in just about two seconds or so.
我们到了。
There we are.
正在下载，我要单击它，或者转到我的下载文件夹并双击。
It's downloading I'm going to click that or head over to my downloads folder and double click.
然而，我希望我能用同样的东西双击这张票，它就会打开
However however I wish I could double click the ticket with the same thing and it's going to open up
这个安装了一个巫师，基本上是要给人通电的。
this install a wizard which were just going to basically power through guys.
因此，我将在这里单击“下一步”。
So I'm going to click next here.
将再次单击“下一步”。
Going to click next again.
然后它会问你想把捷径放在哪里。
And then it will ask you where do you want to put some shortcuts.
我只会在我的开始菜单和桌面上有一个令人震惊的东西，但我真的不想要一个
I'm just going to have a shocker in my Start Menu and on the desktop but I don't really want one in
快速启动栏，但请确保这里有这个。
the quicklaunch bar but make sure you have this one here.
请确保无论您选择什么，都不要取消选中寄存器堆关联，只需在该选项上打勾即可。
Make sure whatever you choose just don't uncheck register file associations just leave that with a tick.
好的，这一点必须保持不变。
OK that must stay the same.
根据您希望将系统设置在您想要快捷方式的位置，与其他人一起玩耍。
Be play around with the others depending on how you want your system set up where you want the shortcuts.
这真的无关紧要。
It doesn't really matter.
无论如何，您都可以删除它们，但是您知道自己的喜好，然后继续并单击下一步。
You can remove them anyway but you know your preference then go ahead and click next.
它会说，嘿，我们可能需要访问您的网络接口。
It's going to say hey we might need to access your network interface.
只要说是就行了，不管怎么说，不用担心。
Just say yes don't worry about that whatsoever.
然后单击Install(安装)。
And click install.
它可能会给我们弹出窗口。
It might give us the pop ups.
继续，对弹出的任何弹出窗口单击是，或单击安装或仅授予其任何权限
Go ahead and click yes to any pop ups that come up or click install or just give it permission whatever
它的意思是，你只管去做就行了。
it means just go ahead and do it.
它将使虚拟虚拟机器能够让您的虚拟机访问
It's just going to be giving virtual virtual box the ability to have your virtual machines access the
互联网，这通常是一个有用的功能。
Internet which is usually a useful function.
因此，只要对它要求的任何内容单击“是”，它就会进入“Installation Complete”(安装完成)屏幕
So just click yes to whatever it asks for and then it will come to the installation complete screen
这里会有一个勾选框，上面写着“安装后启动虚拟框”(Start Virtual Box After Installation)。
and there'll be a tick box here that says start virtual box after installation.
确保其中有一个勾号，然后单击Finish，它将继续并打开一个虚拟框。
Make sure that that has a tick in it and click Finish and it will go ahead and open up a virtual box.
好了，伙计们，这就是你安装虚拟盒子的方法。
There you are guys that's how you go ahead and install virtual box.
很好，很容易。
Nice and easy.
单击“处理”。
Click click click click click process.
现在我们已经继续并在下一个视频中安装了虚拟盒，我们向您展示了如何设置
So now that we've gone ahead and install virtual box in the next video we showed you how you can set
安装您自己的Linux虚拟机。
up your own Linux virtual machine.
所以观看这段视频的朋友们，你们现在已经在你们的机器上安装了虚拟盒。
So folks watching this video guys you've now got virtual box installed on your machine.
让我们继续为您设置Linux。
Let's go ahead and set you up with Linux.